brandymelville.co.uk 2019-01-26

# Privacy Notice

Brandy Melville Online Limited is the sales and distribution provider of Brandy Melville in the UK, Ireland and France.

This Privacy Notice covers the information Brandy Melville Online Limited collects from users and visitors of <https://www.brandymelville.co.uk/>  and related sites and services (also referred to as ‘the Service’). We respect your right to privacy and are committed to protecting your privacy by securely and transparently handling your personal information. This privacy policy sets out details regarding the information that we may collect from you and how we may use that information.

By using the Service and agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you are consenting to the collection, use, disclosure and other handling of your information as described below. 

If you live in the European Economic Area, the Controller of your personal data while using the Services is Brandy Melville Online Limited, and its principal place of business is located at:

Brandy Melville Online Limited, 142 Clock Tower Road, Isleworth, London TW7 6DT United Kingdom

**Information we collect from you**

We may collect from you or ask you to provide certain Personal Information (also known as ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ or ‘PII’).  
Personal Information may include: your name, email, phone number, billing and/or mailing addresses, and credit card or similar financial information we need to process your purchase order, and the IP address you use to access our site. 

**Information Provided/Submitted by Yo** **u**

• Contact details, such as name, address, email address and phone number;  
• Shipping address and billing address;  
• Credit card and payment information

**  
Information We Get From Your Use of Our Services**

The Personal Information we also collect when you use the Service may include information that we ask you to provide directly, information that is collected automatically while you are using our sites and services (please see our Cookies Policy for more details), and/or information that is shared with us by third parties such as hosting and mail service providers.

 **How we use your personal information** Brandy Melville Online Limited may use your Personal Information to do any of the following:

• Create and manage your account when you register, use or purchase a product  
• Verify your identity to allow access to your account  
• Provide you with technical and customer support  
• Communicate with you and manage your delivery  
• Evaluate and improve the quality of our products, services and websites  
• Provide you with a customized experience when you visit our website;  
• Allow us to comply with any applicable law  
• Enforce our legal rights or comply with legal requirements.

**What legal basis do we rely on to process your Personal Information?** The following describes the legal basis on which we will process your Personal Information:

 **Consent**

We ask for your consent to provide you with our promotional material and your Personal Information will be processed for this purpose. You have the right to withdraw consent at any time.  We will stop processing data after consent is withdrawn, where consent is the only legal basis for processing.

 **When you fulfil a contract**

Brandy Melville Online Limited will also process your Personal Information when we need to fulfil a contract with you such as sending your delivery.

 **Legitimate Interest**

Brandy Melville Online Limited also processes your data when it is in our legitimate interests to do so and when these interests are not overridden by your data protection rights.

 **The processing is necessary because of a legal obligation that applies**

Brandy Melville Online Limited may process your data to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations.

 **Your Rights**

Whenever you use our services, we strive to provide you with access to your personal information that we process. Moreover, you can update any information if that is not correct or request that we delete or remove it from our system – unless we are obliged to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes.

You have additional rights such as the right to restrict the processing of your personal data in certain ways, to obtain a copy of your personal information in a commonly used electronic format, to object to certain processing of your personal information by us (including to opt out of any marketing communications that we may send you), and to ask for your data to be made portable.

If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please contact us using the contact details listed  below. For the protection of your privacy and security, our data protection team shall take every reasonable step to ensure that your identity is verified before granting access, or rectification, or deletion.

 **Accessing and deleting your Personal Information**

When you create an account and log in to your account area, it is protected by your password. You can manage the content and information in your account at any time. You are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You can deactivate or delete your account at any time.  
However, if you would like to permanently delete your account, you can send an [email](mailto:online@brandymelville.co.uk?subject=Account%20Deletion%20Request) (online@brandymelville.co.uk) to our Data Protection Team with the subject line “Permanently delete my information and account”. Please do not forget to tell us who you are.

 **Who do we share your Personal Information with?**

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of Brandy Melville Online Limited unless one of the following requirements is met:

**• With your consent** \- We will share Personal Information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Brandy Melville Online Limited.  
 **• For external processing** – We will provide Personal Information to our processors based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate security measures. We Brandy Melville Online Limited may share your Personal Information with third parties such as hosting providers, analytic platforms, and email service providers.  
 **• For legal reasons** \- We will share Personal Information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Brandy Melville Online Limited if we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary.

We may share your Personal Information with third parties such as hosting providers, analytic platforms, and email service providers.

 **Storage of Information and International Transfers**

All Personal Information which you supply to us is generally stored and kept on our secure servers inside the European Economic Area.

However, due to the nature of our global business and the technologies use, your Personal Information may be transferred to our approved third party service providers, subcontractors and partners outside the EEA, in countries where there may be a lower legal level of data protection. In such situations, we have put in place technical and security measures to: prevent the loss or unauthorised access of your personal information including transfer the minimum amount of data necessary, anonymise it where possible, and enter legal contracts with the aim of ensuring that these third parties handle your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the European levels of data protection. However, whilst we have used our best efforts to ensure the security of your information, please be aware that we cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted over the Internet.

 **Managing your Personal Information**

We retain your information as long as your account is active, or as needed to provide your services, or if we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so. We also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. We store your information as long as is necessary for the purpose for which we have collected it. When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your Personal Information, we will either delete or anonymise it or, if it is possible (e.g. your Personal Information is stored in backup archives) then we will securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until the deletion/erasure is possible.

 **How we protect your personal information**

Brandy Melville Online Limited has taken appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized or unlawful access, alteration, loss, damage or destruction. These measures include:  
Physical safeguards with locked doors and file cabinets and controlled access to our facilities and secure destruction.  
Technology safeguards like use of anti-virus and protection software, data encryption and monitoring of our systems and data centers so to comply with our Information security policy including periodically review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures;  
Organisational safeguards like awareness and training on security and privacy to make sure employees understand the importance and measures to protect your data.

 **Third Party Links and Services**

The Services may contain links to third-party websites, applications and services, including social media services, as well as embedded images or other third-party content and features. Your use of these features may result in the collection, processing or sharing of information about you, depending on the feature. We are not responsible for the content, features, security or practices of any third parties. We do not vet, endorse, or make any representations about third parties or their websites, applications or services. The information you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

 **Children and minors**

Brandy Melville Online Limited and its sites and services do knowingly collect information from,  children under the age of eighteen (18). If you discover or are aware that a child under the age of eighteen has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any requests, questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please write to us at:

Brandy Melville Online Limited  
142 Clock Tower Road   
Isleworth, London TW7 6DT  
United Kingdom

Alternatively you can [ email us](mailto:online@brandymelville.co.uk?subject=Privacy%20info%20request)

 **Changes to this Policy**

We may update or amend our Privacy Policy from time to time to comply with the law or to meet our changing business requirements. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will take appropriate measures to inform you, consistent with the significance of the changes we make. By continuing to access the Website and using the Services, your access and use will be subject to those updates and amendments. Please review any changes to this Policy carefully.
